<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ghost Note</title>
    <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ghost Note</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 | Follow on &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ghostnotepony&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 01:35:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ghostnotepony.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brief thoughts on recent fan noise issues</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/fannoise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 01:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/fannoise/</guid>
      <description>Silent Lucidity..? As I mentioned in a recent blog post, an issue that I had with my new workstation was that it was making a lot of excessive noise whenever the slightest load would be put on the processor. I mentioned the Dark Rock Slim in the post and that&amp;rsquo;s what I ended up installing. That install was quite educational and went really well..just took a long time; it involved removing every cable that was plugged in and removing the motherboard itself from the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brief thoughts on CMR vs. SMR in ZFS</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/zfs-smr-cmr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 20:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/zfs-smr-cmr/</guid>
      <description>Well..I got lucky.. As the title says, I did indeed get lucky recently as I happened to get a very timely reminder (as the return window for the drive was about to close..) about CMR and SMR drives. I had learned a while back that the latter is quite nonperformant and potentially unreliable when used in ZFS, as these benchmarks demonstrate. I honestly had not thought of that factor when researching drives for my new ZFS mirror, though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on my new workstation/server conversion</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/newtech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/newtech/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Well, it&amp;rsquo;s been quite a while since I wrote anything on this site..and quite a lot has happened in the world (massive understatement, I know) and in my own life. I&amp;rsquo;ve talked about those things (mostly) as they happened on my Twitter, so if you are curious as to what I am referring to, head over there and have a look. (In summary, I discovered my bisexuality/queerness, I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten a lot of pony art commissioned/embraced wanting to be an adorable little unicorn, I&amp;rsquo;ve struggled immensely with anxiety but have made tremendous progress, especially lately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Brony Identity</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/brony-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 07:07:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/brony-identity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I can&amp;rsquo;t say exactly when it all began, but at some point in late 2010/early 2011, I became aware of the brony fandom. My initial reaction was unfortunately typical: &amp;ldquo;What is this?! Well, it&amp;rsquo;s probably going to be like this one meme that just happened (The Big Lebowski re-written in a Shakespearean fashion) and will disappear/be forgotten in a month&amp;rsquo;s time like that one did.&amp;rdquo; When it didn&amp;rsquo;t vanish as I expected, I was more surprised than irritated at being wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Doctor Who Season 11</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/doctorwhos11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 13:13:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/doctorwhos11/</guid>
      <description>I got into Doctor Who when Russell T. Davies was the showrunner and David Tennant was the Doctor..at that point, I thought it was delightfully weird and not quite like anything that I&amp;rsquo;d seen before. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t rearranging my schedule to watch it but I had it set to record on my DVR and liked to watch a few in a row if I had the time. Then Steven Moffat took over the show and I noticed things started changing almost immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Fields of Gold and Rainbow</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/fog-rainbow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 22:20:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/fog-rainbow/</guid>
      <description>Now that things have (kind of) settled down for me, I want to get my thoughts on the first two songs I&amp;rsquo;ve released written while they&amp;rsquo;re (relatively) fresh in my mind.
Fields of Gold Back in the 90s, I was rather confused musically (along with being confused in general). I was just starting to get into metal after a childhood of almost nothing but classical and the pop music of the day (of course, I still love 80s/early 90s pop if just due to the nostalgia factor) and I was starting to disdain anything that I thought was &amp;lsquo;too light&amp;rsquo; (a lot of which I love now, naturally).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on World of Warcraft</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/wow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 23:40:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/wow/</guid>
      <description>I think it was about 10-11 years ago that I started regularly playing Blizzard&amp;rsquo;s seminal MMORPG, World of Warcraft. Back then, I had enormous amounts of free time (that seem mostly wasted, in retrospect) but I did have a lot of fun playing WoW during that time. Of course, as time went on, my life changed significantly for the better but I still tried to fit in playing whenever I could.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on fandoms and public relations</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/fandom-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 12:42:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/fandom-pr/</guid>
      <description>Several weeks ago, I was randomly looking around Twitter (I know, a wonderful use of one&amp;rsquo;s time) and happened upon a reply in a long thread which stated that &amp;ldquo;(our fandom) has terrible PR.&amp;rdquo; So that got me thinking..and as usual, I thought it over for quite a while and came to the conclusion that (if they weren&amp;rsquo;t just glumly kidding..I have a hard enough time telling if people are doing that in real life, let alone the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on concern trolls and trolling in general</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/concern/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 20:53:27 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/concern/</guid>
      <description>This is something I&amp;rsquo;ve been pondering for quite a while, and now is as good a time as any to write it all down.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been around the Internet a long time and I&amp;rsquo;ve seen..well, just about everything (and a lot of things I never wanted to see, but that&amp;rsquo;s life in general). In the early 2000s, I started hanging around political blogs and while I don&amp;rsquo;t remember saying all that much, I felt like I could if I needed to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekends</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/weekends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 10:38:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/weekends/</guid>
      <description>One of the biggest changes in going from &amp;ldquo;single guy&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;family man&amp;rdquo; is that the weekend, once the thing that got one through a tough week, is now..something else entirely. It&amp;rsquo;s not &amp;lsquo;my&amp;rsquo; time anymore, it belongs to my wife and children as well. It was a harsh adjustment at first, of course (especially when the first child arrived and everything changed, but now that I&amp;rsquo;ve set my expectations for what a weekend entails accordingly, I can handle it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Beginning</title>
      <link>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:20:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ghostnotepony.github.io/posts/beginning/</guid>
      <description>For when Twitter isn&amp;rsquo;t enough to contain my rants..now there&amp;rsquo;s this site. Also announcements about any songs I&amp;rsquo;ve posted to YouTube..(no ETA on any of those just yet.) Along with anything else I might think of..</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
